Okay, the next defense drill we'll discuss is on the ball defense.
When the ball is picked up by your defender, whether they're getting ready to pass or shoot it, what you want to do, as soon as the ball is picked up, you need to be all up on them, in their face.
Hands up, hands in the face to block their view from passing or shooting.
And wherever they take the ball, one hand needs to be there.
If the ball goes to their left side, put the hand by the ball and keep one hand in the face.
Same with the opposite side.
Keep one hand in the face and the ball here.
So remember to be--crowd their space as much as possible as soon as they pick up the ball, so they can't move, they can't look, or anything.
And don't forget the distraction.
Because all that's good too.
And this is on the ball defense once the ball is picked up.
So just remember from your stance position, as soon as the ball is picked up, you're here all up on them.
Hands in the face, hands up, crowding the space.
Don't let them see anything or get a pass away or a shot away.
And this is proper on the ball defense when the ball is picked up by your opponent.